this is E on E censored Supernatural
Bible changes on YouTube and today is
the 15th of January 2024 wanted to let
you know that my latest book on
Supernatural Bible changes is available
on Amazon and it's called pandemics
plagues and Supernatural Bible changes
this little book it's 5.75 by6 it has
over
330 Bible verses that have been altered
that have new words in it related
to the
pandemic it's
crazy and in these verses some of them
are complete rewrites but you will see
grammar errors punctuation errors new
words spelling errors new people
doctrinal errors nonsense verses and
More in these verses if you have eyes to
see our bibles are supernaturally
changing and we know from scripture that
the Antichrist would come with lying
signs and
wonders and that God would send the
strong delusion because they did not
love the truth and there would be a
great falling away and what's happening
with these Bible changes that are
prolific on every single page of
scripture is that the Antichrist is
rising we were told in 2 Thessalonians 2
that he would pretend that he is God and
I believe personally that these changed
to scripture are in fact the abomination
of desolation standing in a holy place
it's truly diabolical it's time to wake
up in Jesus name let me show you some of
the verses that I show in this book it's
348 pages and here's a verse in 2
Chronicles 21:19 I put one verse on each
page so you can just open it up and just
read and it came to pass that in in
process of
time after the end of two years his
bowels fell out by reason of his
sickness so he made so he died of sore
diseases and his people made no burning
for him like the burning of his fathers
do you recognize any of this
language bowels falling out by reason of
the sickness it came to pass in the
process of time that's all new language
for me what about you he died of sore
diseases and people made no burning for
him what does that even
mean please tell
me but are we not seeing people being
diagnosed with lots of bowel disease
recent bowels is a new word in the Bible
died of sore
diseases there's a lot of new diseases
in the Bible like py for example you
know related to Belle's paly something
that we've been seeing with some people
who have been eating those cupcakes of
recent and again I'm speaking using
creative language
here because the wicked ones do not not
want you to know the truth of how
dangerous the cupcakes are changing your
DNA it's diabolical let me go ahead and
continue showing you other verses that
have changed I'm just going to scroll
down here here's one I'm not going to
read this entire verse to you second
chronicles 34:22 it has new names in it
new people I've never heard of and new
words like
wardrobe but the one that I was really
want to show you was the word College
because we were seeing that colleges
have become complet licit in the lies
and we're seeing colleges push a woke
satanic agenda we're seeing colleges
that are no longer preparing their
students to be
successful they're preparing them
they're brainwashing them with
propaganda that's all I'm going to say
there but I also well one thing I will
say is that colleges are also
pushing the cupcakes
and it's
wicked I've
survived happily for 3 years without any
cupcakes we never needed the cupcakes
they want the cupcakes inside of us
because it changes our
DNA and because they can do updates
because it is technology if you don't
know this you need to do your research
immediately let me go ahead and continue
on here here's one 2 Corinthians 12 ye
are not straightened in us but ye are
straightened in your own
bowels yeah what more can I say this is
a disgusting verse totally Rewritten
straightened in US straightened in your
own bowels
disgusting here's another one 2
Corinthians 9:13 whils by the experiment
of this ministration they glorify God
for your professed subjection into the
gospel of Christ and for your liberal
distribution unto them and into all men
this verse is another rewriting liberal
ministration Wilds not even a word the
experiment and let me just tell you this
has been an experiment the last few
years for something more
Sinister that's going to happen and if
you know you know I'm not trying to
scare you I'm just telling you the way
it is now some of you are right now
wondering how are they doing this I'm
going to tell you they're changing
scripture through black magic it's
frequencies it's wicked it's nefarious
and it's clearly happening that's the
most important thing is that you see
that it's
happening Satan wants us to be consumed
with how it's happening more so than it
is happening and what to do about it but
I'm here to warn the church and anyone
who has ears to hear the Bible is
satanically changing and different
agendas are being plopped in here I
think these are new words and language
in scripture is about sending forth
spells do you understand
incantations
messages and then these weird words are
popping up in real time with
nefarious purposes
intent let me go ahead and show you one
more
and his servants arose and made a
conspiracy and it goes on with other new
words in here 2 Kings 1220 conspiracy is
new in the
Bible and then here's
one another person falling sick of a
sickness whereof he died and we're
seeing a lot of people fall down
dead just
collapse and this too is now all through
scripture if you have eyes to see now
I'm going to go and tell you we have
words like doctors in the Bible in fact
Jesus is now teaching in the temple when
he was 12 years
old do you remember that story it was a
synagogue he was teaching in a synagogue
and he was teaching to the Pharisees and
the religious leaders of that day and
they were in awe they were amazed with
his teaching because he spoke with great
Authority does that ring a bell to you
well now in the Book of
Luke he's no longer teaching instead
he's listening to and asking questions
to
doctors I'm not kidding you and that
verse is also in this book so here is my
um information on Amazon this book is
$14 normally but it's been dropped to
$12 for a short time it has over it has
348 pages in it a lot of scripture
changes related to masking covering up
your face to py to plagues to falling
down dead to uh shots to
vexations to Asia the word Asia is a new
country in the Bible it used to be
called Asia Minor but now it's just Asia
and of course Asia has been all over the
news regarding the recent pandemic it's
time to wake up in Jesus name let me
know if you have any questions thank you
so much brothers and sisters for praying
for me for my
channel and my prayer is that any
content that I put out about the Bible
changes will be used to help you see
more clearly and be tools that you can
use to share the truth of the scripture
changes with your loved ones with your
church with your family with
strangers we are responsible for those
of us who see the obvious change of
scripture we are responsible for warning
others because these
changes are
[Music]
literally
reshaping the Christian church do you
understand because the church is is now
embracing these changes these churches
are being led by Wolves probably
Freemasons being led by wolves and
teaching these perversions now in
scripture as
truth leading to the great falling away
the abomination of
desolation with that said be strong and
courageous brothers and sisters do not
fear or be dismayed for the Lord your
God is with you wherever you go until
next time